# **JOSE BROWN**

SENIOR FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### **PERSONAL**

Name	Jose Brown
DOB	09/10/1993
Relationship	Single
Nationality	Switzerland
Languages	English, Chinese

## CONTACT

PHONE	+ 41762124857
Email	rkvirtys109@gmail.com
Skype	live:.cid.db16316db75643de
GitHub	https://github.com/Brilliantwebdev11 25

#### **PASSIONS**

Table-tennis, Coding, Volleyball

#### SKII I S

SKILLS	
React	
Angular	
VueJS	
TypeScript	
Blockchain	
PHP	
Laravel	
Node.js	
Next.js	

# **Summary**

I have been working as a Web Developer for 6 years in both Front-end and Back-end web development. Also I have good experience in Blockchain and solidity.

And I'm a machine learning expert with very strong knowle

dge in NLP and computer vision applications. Currently, I'm ranked among the top machine learning freelancers.

As a problem solver who loves facing challenges in my work. I'm excited to be at the deployment phase of my career.

rk, I'm excited to be at the deployment phase of my career as a web developer. I'm passionate and ambitious about m y work, and love to be on a team that questions possibilities.

I am looking for a new job opportunity in Full stack develo pment. I will work harder with all my ability and knowledge f or the company.

Congratulations!

# **Work Experience**

# **Front-End Developer**

THE STUDIO BRIDGE

04/ 2016~03/2017

- In the process of Developing Various commercial sites using Wordpess and shopify for the first time, I gained a sense of CMS and improved my UI sense and design skills.
- I used AngularJS to develop a food delivery app with a lot of developers, and although I didn't develop it until the end, the current product is becoming a very popular app in the Philippines.
- In that time, I used Angular4 but now I can use Angular version from 8 to 13, and I developed project smartly and cleanly using main Angular features-MVC, data binding, directives, pipes, Angular Material, CLI and Ngnix and Typescript.

# Full Stack & Blockchain Developer 06/2017~02/2019 Danapay

- Used React.js and Vue.js to build RESTful APIs for Danapay financial business project. I admin side, I used Vue.js and in customer side, I used React. In second version, we used Next.js instead of react.
- Implemented back-end using Node.js in customer side and Laravel in admin side.
- We used AWS for CI/CD, Zenhub, Miro, Github, Jira, Loom, Slack and Microsoft Teams for communication and project management.

Three.js	
Wordpress	
Shopify	
Cypress	
FastAPI	
Python	
Web3.js	
Pytorch	
TensorFlow	

### **Full Stack Developer**

Deversus Software Inc

04/2019~05/2020

- Developed Video chat application using Next.js and Node.js. By using the latest technologies and frameworks, various complex and highly responsive pages were implemented, and by using performance enhancing technologies, a highly optimized and fast site was created.
- For second project, implemented Food Delivery App using React.js and Node.js from scratch and later, developed several small projects using React and Node.
- Implemented back-end using Node.js in customer side and Laravel in admin side.

# Deep learning Engineer

07/2020~09/2020

Proteinea

- Conducted Training, testing and logging pipelines for using Deep learning in predicting protein expression levels using DNA features.

## **Education**

# **Bachelor of Computer Engineering**

2013~2016

Far Eastern University

- Software Development
- Computer Network
- Foundations of Algorithms
- Operating System